and then you are
ready to
do this meditation
so
the idea is that you need a lot of preparation
work so that you can do it well we don't
know
that's not all that you need a lot of thinking
but you need to start something first let's start
first get
ready a little bit what we are going to give
now grandpa will lead you through a short
meditation
where does it mean
wise man
or grandpa
now we will have 10 minutes of group meditation
when you meditate groups
you have more
so you you should have your
cell phone turned off if it is not turned off
please turn it off we are
starting
this week I would like to try a
new
new way to start meditation This is who In
the wild and not 10
I don't know
maybe it will be more distracting
but for me
10 wild species it doesn't work but here it
works it is about 6 minutes So
let's try to
count to a hundred and If you get
frustrated then just continue
where you just closed your eyes we take a
breath
now
think about
interacted yesterday for example
maybe you spent
half an hour with someone in the last few
days choose
one of  such interactions with a person
should have been interacted with a person for half an
hour
[music]
What did you want to get from this interaction
you remember for example I spent the last 5 days
with my wife We went to take
care of my mother I
spent a lot of time with Veronica I
hope that I
hoped
when I was working
on the text myself
it was
inside my mind
you were Next to this person what you
really did and thought at that time
what that person wanted to do at that time
you think
remember What they did what that person
did to others What do
you
think they would like to
do at the time you were together So that
they would enjoy doing when you were together
I think that my wife
was quite focused on helping my mother
she has a list of other people that she
helps I think that she would want to
focus her time on that
[music] you
can sacrifice
what you want to do and do what she
wants the other person
will be very stable for sure You can't
keep doing it all the time You have what
you want to do And that person  is
that what he or she wants to do
or could there be a third alternative and
the groom constantly thinks
about is there a third choice
I know what my wife wants to do
today I know what I want to do
today is there some
smart some smart
advice some creative way so that we can
do together what we want and it will be
smart and so that
we
interact together spend time together day is there something that
we can do together
deeply penetrating what we want Each
of us individually and create a third
possibility of our
relationship our our interaction so that
somehow we together so that
we together would be better than we would be
alone is there a way that I worked on the
student's text on this translation of this
text and
also
served my mother and
Veronica did what she wants to
serve her clients we both have
equal rights to
do what we want is there some kind of
creative way creativity way to
help each other do what
each of us wants
and do it better than if we did
it alone or at the expense of another person
and this is a
way of life Because your hundred
does not sacrifice what he wants to do
he does not  makes
selfish what he wants to do he
finds a creative way so that
everyone gets what they want at the same time
think about this interaction
about a third
choice than in addition to these two choices
somehow so that you can achieve what you
want These two people at the same time
You have the same day
What we did with my wife
we ​​took time in the morning she likes to walk
By the ocean
California she
went for walks along
the coast and we
and she could collect
and make lists of things that she would like to
do today and I
worked on translating for myself at the time
then we
combined our lists She
showed that she had a list of people
where we should help together I also
have such a list we
spent time so that we could combine these lists
together to
spend the day together
washing Would you be able to do something like this
with the person
you are thinking about right now this is a very
creative way such a middle way between
doing what the
other wants and more between what you want to
do such a middle way so that everyone
gets what they want and no one
sacrifices so that it is also in an equal
degree counted taken into account
and gradually open  your eyes
turn around stretch
if you're like me then i think i
remember when i first came to
diamond game there
were about 80 students we came here to
study diamond way together
they
went through 7 years of training in new york
7 years of diamond way and we
finished it together we had a
graduation many did a three year
rite and now 200 thousand students in around the
world about 15 organizations
around the world
and so
starting from 80
we grew to 200 thousand in my time
that's about that's what increased
i
can't
do with my wife
and for each of the two 100 thousand
students
what i did for
8-10 students
here some of my old friends are turning 80
they sometimes ask me can i come for
an hour
[music]
to you and i say no
now times have changed
seeds the grain has changed
i.e. from two states of all reasons you
can't just like with
87 students it's also easy to
communicate with mine they calculated if you
give each one at least one hour
it will  16 years
is not More
intelligent and time management because time
it is also empty time so it can
be increased to stretch
and I said Einstein
and he even proved it
the speed of light
that goes to the
earth It changes
from Mercury
Mercury slows down
when there light goes through such a tube into
space It has a curvature light
slows down goes longer to us that is
when you see on Mercury it means that
you are looking at the past you would me directly
now travel in chat the past and the new
telescope - it
shows that it is directly very
very true you can directly
observe the past
and the method or cut it turn on all
people at the same time
it has to do
For the emptiness of time and just
simply
We create time we
and do not play with space and then we
can
help more number of beings there are two
types hydrogen So look
helping each other for me it is
impossible sometimes to
do
meet the needs of two thousand people
this week it is impossible Unless I
work with frequency that is I think that
you
these tools are very important I think that
Why did he start the discussion  with a false
parent this means that you first have to
start from this and then come to
the true homeland otherwise you will not
be able to serve all living beings you will not
be able to satisfy the desires of every
living being and give them
equal time
only if you do not know how to play with this
time first you have to develop this
desire to help all human beings and
this leads you to the fact
that you have such a need to invent
some invention
and
[music]
invent a way
developed such a way the ability to
help others and in fact your
ability to help others it is
incredible it is
limitless and we have to push ourselves
in this direction now we have 10 minutes
for your questions and
how do you want to spend it in this room or
online so let's start with the room